<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Annual Summary on DSkrzypiec Blog</title>
    <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/tags/annual-summary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Annual Summary on DSkrzypiec Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dskrzypiec.dev/tags/annual-summary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Summary of 2024</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/year2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/year2024/</guid>
      <description>Intro Time flies! It&amp;rsquo;s time to summarize the year 2024. For additional context you might want to check the summary of 2023.
Running paused The beginning of 2024 (January, February) was a period of intense running training in preparation for the Warsaw Half Marathon. I intended to achieve a time below 2 hours (around 1:50) in this race. Unfortunately, at the beginning of March, pain around the knee and tension in the quadriceps muscle prevented further training.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of 2023</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/year2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/year2023/</guid>
      <description>Continuation of 2022 I would like to start by mentioning the things I continued doing in 2023, beginning with sports. I maintained my running routine, pursued table tennis training, and practiced fundamental calisthenics, including pull-ups, push-ups, and dips. However, I decided to discontinue my Russian language studies, mostly due to lack of time. As for my MacBook Air M1 from 2020, it&amp;rsquo;s still in pretty decent condition, even after nearly three years of heavy usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of 2022</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/year2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/year2022/</guid>
      <description>Continuation of 2021 highlights As the first highlight of year 2022 I wanted to mention the continuation of most of habits that I&amp;rsquo;ve started in 2021. I&amp;rsquo;m still jog regularly. I tried to learn Russian somehow regularly over the year. I had some breaks but generally I learned a bit and didn&amp;rsquo;t forget what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned in 2021. I still do pull ups and chin ups on daily basis. I&amp;rsquo;ve run three (3km, 6km and 6km) Runmageddons in 2022!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of 2021</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/year2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/year2021/</guid>
      <description>Started jogging In January, after a long pandemic home isolation I&amp;rsquo;ve started jogging. For my whole life I always hate jogging. I love most sports but running was something else. After almost a year in pandemic with gyms being closed and almost no going outside I though that I&amp;rsquo;ll give it a try.
At first two tries I couldn&amp;rsquo;t run 500 meters without a break for catching a breath. Unexpectedly body adaptation was very quick!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of 2020</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/year2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/year2020/</guid>
      <description>Intro Starting from this year on I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make a post per year with summary of my personal and professional important events within the year.
2020 highlights  Finished application for a factoring company SARS-CoV-2 Changed team and position at work I&amp;rsquo;ve started learning Russian I&amp;rsquo;ve build a PC Całka died My daughter was born  Finished application for a factoring company In April 2020 I&amp;rsquo;ve finished working on the project for a factoring company.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
