<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on DSkrzypiec Blog</title>
    <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on DSkrzypiec Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dskrzypiec.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Summary of 2020</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/year2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/year2020/</guid>
      <description>Intro Starting from this year on I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make a post per year with summary of my personal and professional important events within the year.
2020 highlights  Finished application for a factoring company SARS-CoV-2 Changed team and position at work I&amp;rsquo;ve started learning Russian I&amp;rsquo;ve build a PC Całka died My daughter was born  Finished application for a factoring company In April 2020 I&amp;rsquo;ve finished working on the project for a factoring company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Database</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/home-db/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/home-db/</guid>
      <description>Intro Last month after my daughter was born we&amp;rsquo;ve received a bunch of documents in this matter. Birth certificate, medical papers, assignment of PESEL, etc. When I was about to put those papers into document folders I thought it&amp;rsquo;s time for digitalization.
Most of our very important documents like mortgage papers or university diplomas exist only in physical version without any copy either digital or physical. We had plans to scan or at least make photos of those but we didn&amp;rsquo;t do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Całka</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/calka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/calka/</guid>
      <description>Intro Last Saturday, 17th October 2020, Całka (one of my two cats) had to be put to sleep. Name Całka translates from Polish to English as Integral. I and my (at that time) girlfriend were maths undergrads when we&amp;rsquo;ve taken Całka from an animal shelter in early 2016. That probably explains the name.
For the last two months, Całka fought with really nasty jaw bone cancer. It was growing fast. It was too big to even consider surgery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mocking a file system in Go</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/mock-go-filesystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/mock-go-filesystem/</guid>
      <description>src  config  config.go config_test.go reloader.go   dir  dir.go dir_test.go dirCompare.go dirCompare_test.go hash.go listener.go   loop  mainLoop.go   main.go   readme.md  Intro In this post we&amp;rsquo;ll try to mock some features of a file system in Go. We&amp;rsquo;ll focus mainly on file tree structure instead on IO operations on files itself. If you are interested in full abstract file system for Go check out afero package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a small form factor PC</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/minipc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/minipc/</guid>
      <description>Intro At the beginning I want to say, thank you, to Tymek for introducing me into SFF and general building a PC area. He also gave me a lot of tips and advices which surely saved me many hours of reading hardware specs.
For last ten years I&amp;rsquo;ve been using laptops as my main interface for programming and browsing Internet. Reason for that was me being a student for whom battery life and device&amp;rsquo;s weight was more important than better specs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing a blog on smartphone</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/smartphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/smartphone/</guid>
      <description>Intro Nowadays smartphones are basically a pocket computers. Smartphone hardware evolution is very rapid. I was in a situation where my middle-tier phone was better than my current laptop. Could smartphone be used for programming in that case? The answer is yes but is it actual feasible? In this post we&amp;rsquo;ll focus on implementing a blog on a Android smartphone.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using my smartphone to play with C++, Go, Vim and practice UNIX programs like AWK and grep for quite some time now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m quitting cmd</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/quittingcmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/quittingcmd/</guid>
      <description>Background Regarding operating systems I prefer Linux over Windows. Even though in my job I&#39;m forced to use Windows. To make my work on Windows more pleasant I&#39;ve been using Command-line alongside with vim, grep, AWK and other Unix/Linux tools.
Using cmd before Windows 10 was not a very visual appealing experience. It suppose to be just a rectangle box with a text and somehow they made it hard to read and write text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vim Movement Challenge</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/vimmovchallenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/vimmovchallenge/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been using Vim for about 3 years now and I feel very comfortable using it. But recently I&#39;ve got feeling that for a long time I didn&#39;t make any progress regarding my movement in Vim. In those years w\W, b\B, e\E, t, f, /, ?, $, ^, 0, } and G were my best friends for making fast and precise moves in normal mode. Don&#39;t get me wrong. With those I&#39;m happy and still can finish editing much more quicker than in standard text editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My favorite tech talks</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/favtechtalks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/favtechtalks/</guid>
      <description>Intro I want to share with you a list of my favorite tech talks. I can honestly say this is my hobby. Watching tech talks on YouTube. Here I&#39;ve prepared list of eleven my most liked presentations. For each of them I try to describe why those are special to me and why their are worth watching. Order of titles is not particularly important.
I wanted to keep this list pretty short (around 10) therefore it&#39;s not complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go database/sql vs jmoiron/sqlx reading benchmark</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/gosqlstdsqlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/gosqlstdsqlx/</guid>
      <description>Intro While building most of projects or apps it is very common to read from a database. In go standard way to do that is by using database/sql standard library. To illustrate how it can be done let&#39;s load from database a bunch of Points which are slice of Points defined as follows
 type Point struct { X int Y float64 } type Points []Point  Next listening contains definition of function ReadPoints which for existing *sql.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What the quantile really is?</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/quantiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/quantiles/</guid>
      <description>Intro For few years when I was practicing data science I&#39;ve used quantiles a lot. I knew what it is and when one should use it. I knew mathematical definition and intuition around quantiles but if someone would ask me to implement it from scratch I wouldn&#39;t know how to do it right away.
So what is a quantile? It&#39;s a one of most commonly used descriptive statistic. It gives us aggregated information about sample&#39;s distribution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>About this blog Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Damian Skrzypiec and this is my blog. I write mostly about mathematics and programming in general.
About me I live in Warsaw in Poland. I&amp;rsquo;m math graduate but my main interest is programming and computer science. Currently my main language is Go alongside with C#. I like C++ a lot but unfortunately I didn&amp;rsquo;t work with it professionally. I use Python for scripting and R for stats and data mining.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
