<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ppacer on DSkrzypiec Blog</title>
    <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/tags/ppacer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ppacer on DSkrzypiec Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dskrzypiec.dev/tags/ppacer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Releasing ppacer v0.0.1</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/ppacer001/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/ppacer001/</guid>
      <description>The News I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce that the first ppacer release is out! That is literally version v0.0.1. Please check the GitHub release to get the full list of features and changes: v0.0.1 on GitHub.
Is It Ready Then? Of course it is not. Version v0.0.1 was focused on making the backend stable enough and with a minimal set of features to be used by users, including myself. To be clear, there is no frontend yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing cron</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/cron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/cron/</guid>
      <description>Intro Recently, I have been documenting ppacer schedules and in that moment I thought I should have probably implemented cron schedule for ppacer. Before I explain why, let&amp;rsquo;s take one step back to give you a bit of context about ppacer schedules. Schedules in ppacer are covered by generic and simple interface
type Schedule interface { Start() time.Time Next(current time.Time, prevSched *time.Time) time.Time String() string } Initially I&amp;rsquo;ve provided the simplest possible regular schedule which satisfies that interface - schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing ppacer: yet another DAG scheduler which I prefer</title>
      <link>https://dskrzypiec.dev/ppacer-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dskrzypiec.dev/ppacer-intro/</guid>
      <description>Intro As I mentioned in New Scheduler, in the second half of 2023 I started working on implementing new scheduler in Go. In this post I wanted to share with you the current status of the project, next steps and few links.
The name: ppacer At the end of the previous year I was already working already for 4-5 months on this project but still I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a name for it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
